<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Practical Examples on UEB cluster usage tutorial</title>
    <link>https://angelueb.github.io/clustertut/practical-examples/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Practical Examples on UEB cluster usage tutorial</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:19:13 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://angelueb.github.io/clustertut/practical-examples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pre-installed software: RNA-Seq QC</title>
      <link>https://angelueb.github.io/clustertut/practical-examples/example_pre-installed/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:19:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://angelueb.github.io/clustertut/practical-examples/example_pre-installed/index.html</guid>
      <description>Pre-installed software: RNA-Seq QC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singularity: Quasi-mapping RNA-Seq quantification</title>
      <link>https://angelueb.github.io/clustertut/practical-examples/example_singularity/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:19:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://angelueb.github.io/clustertut/practical-examples/example_singularity/index.html</guid>
      <description>The use of Singularity containers is supported in the cluster. In contrast to other container technologies, Singularity is a good fit to HPC environments, since:
Singularity containers don&amp;rsquo;t need administrative privileges to be executed. Performance levels are very close to regular binaries. Compatibility with Docker images, which enables the use of a huge number of readily available existing containerized tools. Container building tools similar to Docker. Users can build custom containers using already acquired general principles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPU job: RL-Medical with conda</title>
      <link>https://angelueb.github.io/clustertut/practical-examples/example_gpu-conda/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:19:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://angelueb.github.io/clustertut/practical-examples/example_gpu-conda/index.html</guid>
      <description>Although Singularity is the recommended way to run tools on the cluster without the need of requesting administrators a system-wide installation, you can also use Conda-based installations and environments. Please note that, as with any other kind of user-level locally installed and run software, we can offer limited support.
Installing Miniconda We are going to install Miniconda, which is a lightweight Conda distribution. We recommend it since Miniconda initial installation requires much less disk space than the full Conda distribution, and disk space on the cluster is a limited resource, (of course, with Miniconda you can install additional packages whenever you need them).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>